<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Smart_E_Voter</string>
    <string name="para">
        <b>1.Eligibility : </b>
        Voters must meet the eligibility criteria established by the relevant electoral authority. This may include age requirements,
        citizenship status, and residency within the voting jurisdiction.
        \n\n
        <b>2.Identification : </b>
        Voters may be required to verify their identity before casting their vote. Acceptable forms of identification
        include voter registration cards.
        \n\n
        <b>3.Voter Registration : </b>
        In jurisdictions where voter registration is required, voters must ensure that they are registered to vote prior to the
        election or voting day. Failure to register within the specified deadline may result in ineligibility to vote. So the voter ensure
        that they are registered by administrator.
        \n\n
        <b>4.Secrecy of the vote : </b>
        Voters must maintain the secrecy of their vote by marking their choices in private as instructed. Sharing or disclosing
        the contents of one vote is strictly prohibited.
        \n\n
        <b>5.Compliance with Instructions : </b>
        Voters must comply with the instructions provided by election officials. This includes following the procedures for
        casting a vote and adhering to any rules specific to the voting.
        \n\n
        <b>6.Respect for the Election Process : </b>
        Voters should respect the integrity of the electoral process and refrain from any behavior that undermines public
        confidence in the fairness of the election.
        \n\n
    </string>
    <string name="result_display">Result Display ...</string>
    <string name="scan">Scan</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">voter fragment</string>
    <string name="qrcode">Please scan this below code while you are committed to the voting process for an authentication purpose.</string>
    <string name="ins">Please provide all the information that are required here.</string>
    <string name="voteinfo">Please authenticate with fingerprint, QRCode and One Time Password to cast your vote more <b>Securely.</b>\n\n
        When your are going to vote, you must have voter id that are provided by the admin for QRCode scan and you must have a phone for an OTP also verify that
        the number is provided by you to the Admin.
    </string>
    <string name="best">All the best to your vote.</string>
</resources>